Workers United Photographs 6284 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Workers United Photographs
2009-2009
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Workers United
6284 P
1.11 cubic feet
1.1 linear ft.
Photographs.
7130122
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 14, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 25, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6284: Workers United Records 6284 AV: Workers United Audiovisual Materials 6284 G: Workers United Poster 6284 MB: Workers United Memorabilia 6284 PUBS: Workers United Publications 6284(d): Workers United Records (digital)
Hotel Employees & Restaurant Employees International Union; Service Employees International Union; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; UNITE HERE (Organization); Workers United
7130122
- Photo CD (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Unite Rally and Miscellaneous photos (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Unlabeled photo album (Box 2, Folder 2)
- UNITE photos (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Unlabeled Photo album (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Lana (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Child Care Center, Labor Day Parade, Immigration Rally (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Meetings about Health Care (Box 2, Folder 7)
- 8/28 UNITE #4 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Scope and Contents
  Brian w/ER Ted, 6/13/01, UCLA
- Mass Rally - Photo sent out UCLA - 6/13/01, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Folder binding - 8/28 UNITE #5
- City Hall - Hearing on Tax Dollars (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Rally (Check-in/May) c.2000 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- National Labor Committee - Protest 1998-2005 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Assorted events (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Assorted events (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Assorted events (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous Photos - labeled 'Random' (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous Photos - labeled 'Random' (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Miscellaneous Photos - labeled 'Random' (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Assorted events (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Shop Photos -- c/2000-2005 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Local 155 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Assorted Photos (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Triangle Fire Display (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Shop Photos -- c/2000-2005 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Retirees Christmas and Chanukah Parties (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Assorted events (Box 2, Folder 26)
- UNITE Convention Delegates (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Folklore Festival 7/2001 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- GIDC - Garment Inventory Development Center 7/2001 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Sherry Kane (Box 2, Folder 30)
- People in shops (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Photos of cultural Week organized by Students in ESL Program (Box 2, Folder 32)
  14 photos
- 8/28 - UNITE #3 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  photo album
- Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance - New York Chapter (Box 3, Folder 2)
- 'Good Jobs, Strong Communities.' (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Local 23-25 UNITE (Box 3, Folder 4)
- UNITE Rally (Box 3, Folder 5)
- UNITE Protest (Box 3, Folder 6)
- UNITE Rally (Box 3, Folder 7)
- March - Hong Kong Returns to China -- 6/30/1997, by David Law (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Performances (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Chinese - NY Cultural Celebration (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Rocky Conference - Retirees Rally (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Labor Day Parade (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Assorted protests (Box 3, Folder 13)
- UNITE Convention June 1999 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Assorted Photos - (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Assorted photos (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Classroom - Salon de (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Lidia Correa (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Assorted photos (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Miscellaneous photos (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Miscellaneous Meeting Photos (Box 3, Folder 21)
- UNITE Photos (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Assorted Factor Pictures (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Triangle Factory Fire Pictures (Box 3, Folder 24)